What is Dropbox shilling is a fulfillment model that allows you to buy products individually from a
little sailor and ship them directly to your customer.
Instead of purchasing a large amount of that you've been to you're simply partnered with a drug specialty
supplier and their messengers for us.
The supplier will ship doctor directly from their warehouse to your customer address and charge you
only for the price of the shipping item that's spoiled.
And we see the customer are looking for their Web site choose the item then it drops over as you will
receive the order and then actually you wouldn't buy it from your supplier.
After that supplier exactly will be shipped dealer item to your customer.
So this is the cycle of that.
This is the life cycle of that job.
Big drop shipping.