Hi welcome to the new lecture of the hour.
How do you use the odd awards to make some specific niche of your products and that this will help you
to show up.
How how to add in your products.
You start to see the most was it the most with.
Which up with the results on the search engine or on either side.
Exactly.
We know that Google Adwords needs to create an account to share my money way with advertising by Schorling
get sites.
But at this point or at this moment with this mixture we are using Google AdWords to show that slice
and that each of each keywords or that each of them that's a name for us for a search engine.
Does this product or this or this.
This q.
And then on the Internet.
So let's go up to that.
Let's go to that.
Two is you're going to do click Tools then do more with your odds precede their results as example as
shown here.