Say OK it's awesome.
Really it's awesome result.
OK we got an average monthly session for all ideas from 1 million to 10 million people of the word search
on this war.
In this regard we see that it was under my charge was that 100 to 100 to 1000 high with that competition
and we didn't need to just bet.
So this is for the campaigns.
If we we she wants to work with the rewards.
But that as I mentioned before here and I'm coming here to show at the end of all that data the polling
data for this for this product that also I can't I have to add on another war with our fight with dad.
Once again it is the result of the charms from 100 to 1000 high.
Hello.
Here we see the competition.
This guy again here.
This is the if you loved
your show up your block is empty and there are a blogger who wants to enter.
We don't need to go to the.
If you plan.
Let's come back again here.
Uber that's for a.
Just go to our galaxy s simple example.
And Click here to get ideas.
To show up the results.
But this projectile within him often connects the essence of a
rigourously.
Exactly.
Very much sir.
This bet sure that edge for settling get access to over 100 to 1 million high.
OK.
What is the British to be exactly a high search engine and high traffic wave the big volume data.
We've got Samsung Galaxy S does from one hundred to one thousand medium no media.
Let's go to this scroll down to show up.
Look I can't it's got to show up like something like this one.
Oh my God.
Samsung Galaxy S 7 5 6 2 with the result from 10 to 100.
OK let's go to settings for other products as example.
IPhone 6 as an example.
It's not just yes your honor that is all for iPhone 6.
It's.