Hi welcome to the new lecture of the section I discover we are going to set up shop with some express
look come on the Amazon Dot com.
Let's begin with with the site of Alecs the rest of the here.
Here's the site or at Express.
You see the category with them different.
That's the other CHONE here.
When you scroll down and we see for different categories.
The front price on accessories.
It.
Claudius furnitures.
There are a lot of categories of work done multiple or that some of thousands of products at the store
of Express.
Now I'm going to do search for specific products.
Let's go to your assertion about the product with the name of
charm's Rozy elements charms make.
I encourage you to make a new account with the express throw to program to get the best price from an
express because of the risk that provides the affiliate program some special prices.
So here we see the BSA results.
Let's scroll down to see more options for who shot up.
Order of about 10 be for that.
With the prices you get some from the loaded gun.
OK received.
Clear.
See thoroughly it works OK with the free shipping that's good idea.
Us either of four point six seven.
And to see the other products with the price hope that one point to nine for our loss there will be
screws up.
She examined and mentions Machar's three times to see the other product smell the charms.
For the price of two point ninety nine or so I would do well to either but that's it for me for your
website or store to be with free checking on us so you will see this product with this price.
Look at it to see it.
The price is being a good price.
So when we when we will add these other products to you your to store exactly.
You will keep the price as something different.
So this project as example will be up three point five for that up to make some margins for profit to
you.
Let's go to Amazon to send us along with them.
We've been in with the same products like in any number of Rigaud animal charm's as example.
Now just a click here for enter to see the results of exactly that price on Amazon seems to be something
different than unexpressed.
I can see that these prices went down at 20.
These busy blogs.
Super charm and been done.
It's about seven point ninety five dollars.
OK.
And analysts as well are seeing lower more results.
Again you see the six point five nine it's a scroll down to see.
OK.
We have that the different prices that's with the same category from Express and Amazon.
more low than Amazon.
So that on this is that profit when you add your products from Adisa rest with the with the low price
and you.
You will keep some profits of your weight 10 percent or 5 percent or 10 percent of what you want to
I encourage you to make it a little bit margin for profit.
Exactly.
So that's point.
But before we are going to continue with this with this issue that we're adding get products for your
e-commerce site.
Exactly.
And to do that to do that we have to to check out the products the day bottles of this product from
I'm going to show you how to see that in.
How to see that niche.
How do you see that traffic Hutchie to visit.
How do you see the importance of products at the United States or European countries or other or different
countries.
By using Google Trends and the Google Adwords up that could be on the next lecture.
And that's one for this lecture.
So you get by.