Do it live on and express no invites no name cards from a supplier or on the products which are buying
No.
And missing and no incomplete parts gets feedback from your customer or all the other one or what.
That's good for your self to know the quality before going to make your e-commerce site what you're
actually being done exactly to check and I get from your supply up are some more interesting.
I just find that when you buy any products from CBS or your suppliers you have to about to drop that
customer address for shipping.
But the contract you get exactly will be you for free shipping.
Again I commend you.
You make a lot of the offer for free shipping get to add more money to get more income.
What should be.
That's all.
I see you next section with Mike.