Kind will come down again to acquisition hit and going to the site the site of Google.
And I'm looking with the trends shown here with what I could do to go to that site Google and click
on that.
When you go to the stands.
You can you have the ability to actually go about your topics to show up sites and the visits importance
When the place is over the war like United States with the country as shown here.
We here we have to do to short any topics or any items with interest from all of our countries or specific
countries when he had his examined with either the country or the United States.
And it was show up that all of this Congress business in 10 men to have us take our sport.
But again it's got to a good chance to show up.
How many people invest with these products.
To get more specific question with our products.
It's got to be done to shore up the animal animal charms as example and then act like ends are going
to show up and the result centers turn right on PBS and to see the results with Google Trends.