Get Brasi OK that's OK this is all depends on the month.
The 12 months for one year I go OK let's go down to show if we have the.
If you have any information or any pictures that's all just go to Jamaica and you search with you product
it I'm going God to my God and your assertion for for the new product with the name of the Galaxy S
sivin that's going to show up again.
I'm going to click with your
ok on search terms.
OK.
Let's scroll down here to allow subsets for Galaxy
galaxy 7 as example and of picture other receiver.
This is the product with the name of the galaxy the Esteban with the worldwide spiders and go on contiguous
Oh you are going get.
We are looking for that is all full of insights and social resolve them for this for that with the normal
Galaxy S seven of the world one boss five years ago.
But we know that the Galaxy S 7 was mad though when he was gone.
So he received all the pasta years it appears to be resolved here.
But when we come here to live up to all in 2015 it was see the result appears.
So despite heresy that took Brazil for this project done with this day and we just get Obrador.
This got to scroll down to see more options.
Once again it was the result of my interest by DGM him seated.
OK.
The next time it has to be resolved.
So for this producta then Bangladesh Nibali gonna.
This is ours that relates to the global trends get and see that interest by region from this side of
things that I you to use at Go-Betweens.
God intends to add your famous products which.
Which B which have them more interesting on some region.
Let's go down to shore up their net and Tobeck side.