So I'm going to make some come back from and for that to be galaxy 7 I'm going to order the other product
that kind of all that you'll see as sex with the cut out of the lead.
Let's show up the results for twins for each of them with a with a compare the result will be let's
And we see the result of that is sex which men did before right.
Yes.
And you will see the result appears to be more than seven.
OK.
Is that the top result for Galaxia sex.
And is that true.
That's a result of that I see as Sassaman also when we come down here and this could long to show up
Here we see the increased by region with the color of blue and red.
And if I'm going to make it we see with Rusia Rusia Galaxy S seven show up nine years old I guess I
Exactly.
Different places with this not.
So this is the perfect way to show up.
All of the your brother and sister over the war.
And this this issue will help you to choose your brother.
Your best products.
Or so which had.
Which have the a lot of people of a lot of us like I can make different products to combat.
OK.
Put it on iPhone.
IPhone 5.
It's Company OK.
IPhone 5 S.
Click here.
OK.
Now this are let's show up the results by scroll down here.
All right.