You show the results I can see I think an iPhone 5 is different in the interest of going to war.
So most people looks like going to show up the iPhone 5.
It's better than Galaxy 6 or Galaxy S 7.
So this is the best way to combat product to other product.
Like get to see these results.
Also we have the.
Let's go to this wonderful past 90 days.
Also you have to choose a specific region like United States like Canada.
Bad show French or German or other country overlord.
OK there we go.
Exactly.
So within 90 days the goal of the war.
Here we see the iPhone 5 as well as 75 74 points then get access estimate with 60 ads.
And less that.
That's just one.
As I say it.
When you get points.
OK.
There you go.
So we have to show up each of these products with the with specific stocks as John.
He had it with with that colors yellow and red.
And when you come down with this cold dog you will see that galaxy 7 result.
And there was like Dijon Gerken excels at Google Books and Extel Alexander.
Let's go scroll down to show up either result of Azis I'm here with you the Galaxy S6.
Or the color of green and the chop chop.
The countries which are the biggest search for this for.
And this one is iPhone 5.
Yes.
With the map.
And let's read it or let it talk.
So that's all for this for this sight of God ingens.
How do dig up a lot of information about your products.
So this is the site of Google Trends is very important to show about what is the best product to be
added.
When you restore or in your drop Shalane Web site.
So now let's go to the next election to talk more about how do to talk about more about how to use Google
not towards to get more benefits with some awards that's all.
With like.